http://www.pcastructurepoint.com/privacy-policy.asp

Software
spSlab v5.50spBeam v5.50spWall v5.01spColumn v7.00spMats v8.50spFrame v1.50MaintenanceNetwork Licensing
Download & Buy
Buy Now!
Home: Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting STRUCTUREPOINT (“SP”) and reviewing our privacy policy.
SP recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information.
To this end, we are committed to using our best efforts to respect the privacy of our online visitors.
It is our intent to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information received from and about you with your reasonable expectations of privacy.
Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our web site unless you choose to provide that information to us.
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically.
This information does NOT identify you personally.
If you choose to provide us with personal information, SP will collect personally identifiable information such as name, address, email and the like, and use that information to respond to any messages and to help us get you any and all information you have requested.
Be assured that SP strictly protects the security of your personal and proprietary information and honors your choices for its intended use.
We will never sell, rent, or share your information to anyone else.
You may receive information to help you best use the SP site, inform you of changes, updates, or alerts about products you purchase or maintain with SP.
However, we will never send you email unless you request it and we can always remove you from our email list upon receiving your request.
As a resource to our visitors, SP may provide links to other web sites.
We carefully choose web sites that we believe are useful and meet our standards.
Nevertheless, SP cannot guarantee the standards of every web site link, so be advised that once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
Some web sites deposit certain bits of information called "cookies" in a visitor's computer.
The only information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself.
A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.
Cookies are sent back only to the web site that deposited them when a visitor returns to that site.
Most browsers are initially set to accept "Cookies." If you would prefer, you may set yours to refuse them.
However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a web site.
If for some reason you believe SP has not adhered to the principles detailed in this privacy policy, please notify us by email at info@StructurePoint.org and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly.
SP is committed to protecting your privacy and using technology that gives you the most powerful, safe, online experience we can provide.
Any and all changes to this privacy policy will be communicated promptly on this page.
Thank you again for visiting STRUCTUREPOINT.
Software
spSlab v5.50spBeam v5.50spWall v5.01spColumn v7.00spMats v8.50spFrame v1.50MaintenanceNetwork Licensing
Download & Buy
Buy Now!
© 2002 - 2020 STRUCTUREPOINT, LLC.
All rights reserved.
